Ana Chkhaidze: And when you're done you can just end the recording if you want, or I'll just take care of it. Okay, perfect. Thank you.
Ana Chkhaidze: Here.
Ana Chkhaidze: So I guess the 1st thing I kind of noticed was the computer screen kind of looked like it was
Ana Chkhaidze: expanding. I guess the bezel, like the the outside of the computer.
Ana Chkhaidze: Well, it kind of looked thicker than usual, kind of like a like a old TV
Ana Chkhaidze: from like the nineties, like a really old, like box TV. It kind of looked like that. And then it kind of felt like I was looking out of a window instead of looking at a computer screen at just a flashing red light.
Ana Chkhaidze: On the screen, like there were like little traces of shapes. So like I saw a diamond
Ana Chkhaidze: at 1 point just lines going through. I noticed that the longer I stared at the screen the
Ana Chkhaidze: like. It changed colors. So it went from red, and then I saw like orange flashing, and then I would see like it would turn white to feel like white flashing
Ana Chkhaidze: like the longer I standardize it.
Ana Chkhaidze: That's pretty much it.